Now, let's make the top coat.
First, in the process of making the top coat,
change the model pose to T-Pose.
Open Google and select a node,
then click here to open the symmetry edit mode.
The node must be named with the left or right arrow at the beginning
to make the symmetry edit.
Open another node and change the model pose.
Now, let's make the Hanfu version.
After selecting the multi-layer tool,
click on the 2D window to create the starting point.
Press the Shift key and move the mouse
to create the edge of the sleeve.
Press the Shift key and move the mouse to create the edge of the sleeve.
When a curve is completed, release the Ctrl key and press it to create a straight line again.
After completing all the lines, click on the starting point to complete the creation of the board.
Press Ctrl D to create a symmetrical board.
After selecting the front, middle, and back lines, right-click and select Expansion.
Set the diameter of 50mm to be the collar part.
Click on Confirm to complete the expansion.
After selecting two boards, separate them in the 2D window, do not overlap, and it is convenient to arrange them later.
Use the hexagonal tool to draw a line and cut it.
Click on the Rearrange 2D Position tool.
You can arrange the boards in the 3D window according to the placement position in the 2D window.
Expand the back side of the board line to match the front.
The back side does not need to be opened again.
Press the Resize Board tool to be replaced by the Rectangle tool in the下拉菜单.
In the 2D window, click and fill in the height of 50mm and width of 50mm.
Press the Rectangle tool to fill in the height of 50mm and width of 50mm.
pulses in the clicks to create a pallet on the back.
Follow the same pattern as before.
Press the Control D button to create aki board table to М knockout.
To ease the waiting, open Back 3D, This menu shows the Television menu.
Under this display, the back side of Mausoleum will display as Top Mama.
Since the back side has been reorganized, choose an alternative, from Order 2D Wheel Changeポ이에, select the stack block to do your forgot, and turn right to select.
then ajuste its position by a certain value.
After arranging, we start to sew.
After choosing the sewing line, you can choose to sew in the 2D or 3D window.
Once the single machine is adjusted, the sewing line will be completed in the corresponding section of the single machine.
The collar is quite special here, and you have to imagine the position of the seam.
Therefore, the front, middle, and upper parts are on the side of the small rectangle shape.
Then sew all the other parts together.
Like the sleeve and the body, this part of the line is interrupted by a lot of straight lines.
You can use the old sewing machine tool.
Click the starting point and click the end point along the seam line to create the first seam line.
The back is also the same operation.
After sewing, switch back to the cutting board tool and start the simulation.
In order to prevent the back from being unstable, the top and the bottom will be sewn together for the time being.
Use the sewing line tool.
Choose the sewing needle tool in the pull-down menu.
In the 2D window, click and drag the mouse to add the sewing needle near the corner of the rectangle.
After selecting the sewing needle, start the simulation.
While modeling, drag the sewing needle while dragging the sewing needle.
Let the one side of the panel cover the other side of the panel.
After folding, you can hold the sewing machine.
Use a needle to press and pull the sewing machine.
After folding, take off the clothes manually and cover the chest.
If you feel that the collar is wider, you can drag the front and middle lines inward to narrow the collar.
In the dragging process, press the right button to manually enter the movement value.
By moving the line, you can narrow or widen a plate, and other lines on the line will not be affected.
The collar of the back piece is to pull downward from the upper side of the line.
In the simulation process, press the W key to click on the plate, and you can also increase the fixation on the top point.
Drag the fixation to cover the chest of the clothing plate.
To add the sewing line, delete two fixations, press W and click on the fixation again to delete.
Thank you for watching.
Use the free sewing tool to sew the collar together here.
After stabilizing, delete the fixation here on the chest to check the effect.
You can stretch the sewing line to the chest a little longer, so that the clothes can be fixed in more places.
Use the edge sewing tool to drag the edge of the sewing line.
Using the edge sewing tool can also move the entire sewing line to make it closer to the chest.
This will need a lot of work.
Reduce the clip to 11.
Look at the more detailed wrinkle effect.
The clip is narrowed, so add more, and the wrinkles are more subtle.
You can reduce the clip to 11.
In order to obtain a better wrinkle effect, you can change the material and physical properties to other color materials.
For example, you can change to double-layered small-scale sand. This sand can also retain some wrinkle patterns while being softened.
Or you can choose to use O-gain sand, which is a kind of sand with a slightly harder wrinkle and a thicker wrinkle.
Now let's go back to the time when we used O-gain sand.
In the simulation process, you can see that the corners of the side are created due to the creation of the panel. Use the edit panel tool to adjust it.
At the same time, select the points on the panel in the same direction and drag them in the horizontal direction until the curve is smooth.
Then start the simulation.
Since all Hanfu are naturally worn clothes, we need to reduce the surface strength of the model to make the clothes more suitable for the human body.
The total thickness of the clothes is also reduced to 1 to reduce the air thickness around the clothes.
The overall thickness of the clothes is also reduced to 1 to reduce the air thickness around the clothes.